

# **Abdelrhman Ahmed Elnhas**

# Front-End Web Developer - UI/UX Designer - Graphic Designer

🛮 elnhasdesigner@gmail.com 📞 01069277066 👂 Elmahalla Elkubra, Egypt 🏲 Egyptian

in Abdelrhman A. Elnhas 🞧 abdelrhman-elnhas 📙 aedesigns11 🂆 a\_elnhas1 🔟 aelnhas

🖒 abdelrhman\_elnhas 😘 abdelrhman\_elnhas

# Profile

I am Front-End Web Developer since 2021. I've worked on several projects in various fields. Also, I gained some knowledge about Back-End Web Development during working on projects. I am also a UI/UX Designer and a Senior Graphic Designer. I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for technology, especially programming.

#### Education

Faculty Of Engineering, Kafr-Elshiekh University Computers and Control Systems Department

**Public Experimental Language School** 

09/2018 - present Kafr-Elshiekh, Egypt

08/2006 - 07/2018 Elmahalla Elkubra, Egypt

# Primary Education

Canguages

English

German

Arabic

## Certificates

#### Web-Development Internship 🛮

The Sparks Foundation

#### **Introduction to Python**

365 Data Science

### Javascript 🗹

Sololearn

#### **Programming In Python**

# Introduction to Back-

End 🖪

Meta

### **Skills Verification Test For Cascading Style** Sheets (CSS) 2

HackerRank

#### **Responsive Web Design**

Sololearn

#### Introduction to Databases 🖪

**Version Control** 77

Meta

#### **UX Design Fundamentals**

MaharaTech - ITIMooca

Web Development Fundamentals 🗗

Sololearn

### Introduction to **Frontend Development**

Git & Github 🗗 365 Data Science

EF Set 🛮

CSS ra Sololearn

Skills			
HTML5	••••	CSS3	••••
Bootstrap	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$	Javascript	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
Python	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$	Github	••••
PHP	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ$	Laravel	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
Adobe XD	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$	Figma	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$
Adobe Photoshop	• • • •	Adobe Illustrator	••••

### **Professional Experience**

UI/UX Designer

MasterCode

2022 - present

**Front-End Web Developer**MasterCode

2021 – present

Graphic Designer

AE Advertisment

2014 – present

### **♠** Organizations

**Teamwork**2019 – 2020 | Kafr-Elshiekh, Egypt
Head of Media Team

**Life Makers Egypt** 2014 – 2018 | Elmahalla Elkubra, Egypt

Volunteer

The Sparks Foundation
Web Development Intern